你们上周他妈的死哪儿去了
Where the fuck were you last week?
你和麦克开始认真了吗
You and Mike getting serious?
他是我上司  得悠着点儿
No, he's my boss, so we're going slow.
你真的还没跟他睡过吗
You really haven't slept with him?
没  但应该快了
No, but I probably should soon.
太爽了
That was great.
你需要我...帮你做点什么吗
Do you need me to do anything-- something else for you?
就是抚摸你什么的
Touch you or whatever?
不  不  不用  我很好
No, no. I'm--I'm good.
来吧  我们去商场浪荡一下
Let's get slutty and head over to the arcade,
勾搭高中男生
Troll for high school boys.
-你好  -你好  我叫黛比
- Hi. - Hi. Debbie.
我叫马蒂
Matty.
-需要我载你回家吗  -好呀
- Want a ride home? - Sure.
晚安
Have a good night.
斯坦  听说你身体不适
Yo, stan. Hear you're not feeling so good.
斯坦
Stan.
这是搞什么飞机  伙计  他都死了
What the fuck, man? He's dead!
我对这篇论文上的分数有点疑问
I don't understand my grade on this paper.
这是个"D"
That would be a "D."
-那我这论文有什么问题吗  -写得很烂
- What was wrong with it? - Uh, it sucked.
你为什么要选这门课呢
Why are you taking this class anyway?
因为这是唯一一门大一新生
Because it was the only freshman English class
在午后能上的英语课
available after noon.
要是你不想写出比这篇狗屁文章更好的东西
You don't want to work any harder than this piece of shit,
我劝你还是另选其他课的好
I suggest you find yourself another course.
老天  这就是他了
Holy crap, there he is!
他跟你简直一个模子印出来的  亲爱的
He looks just like you, baby!
真挺像  是吧
He kind of does, doesn't he?
你他妈开玩笑吧
You got to be shitting me.
-我怀孕了  -我们会有两个小孩
- I'm pregnant. - We're gonna have two?
这究竟是怎么回事
How is that possible?
大自然母亲有时就是个爱捉弄人的婊子
Mother nature can be a tricky bitch sometimes.
-警察  -举起手来
- Police! - Hands out, now!
-弗兰克  -弗兰克
- Frank? - Frank?
-对  -他真的病得很严重
- Yeah  - He's really sick.
那就病着吧
Oh, he's sick, all right.
他不会惹麻烦的
I don't think he can make it downstairs.
他不会惹事的
He won't be any trouble.
-不行  -我可以照顾他
- No. - I can take care of him.
-不行  -就要
- No. - Yes!
好吧
Fine.
我一喝酒
I have these things in my throat
我喉咙里的东西就会流血
that bleed if I try to swallow alcohol.
所以我得想别的法子把酒输入我的身体
So I have to figure out other ways to get it into my system.
酒倒入这个袋子
Alcohol goes in this bag,
通过这个输入肛门
This goes up the poop chute, and voil
加拉格家的人要喝酒不止一种法子
More than one way to get booze into a Gallagher.
无耻家庭
第四季第二集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  爱卿遛小鸟   君君   重案组李Sir   ztonyy
■
翻译：  扎克不渣   Greentie   青椒   拉图
时间轴：  大喷子   没有影子
■
校对： Greentie      君君
后期： 加森          总监： 落
■
他胳膊上的红疹已经一个多月了
He's had this rash on his arm for over a month now.
是湿疹  不必担心
That's eczema. Nothing to worry about.
带一支药膏回家涂
I'll send you home with a cream.
-你在给谁发短信  小黛  -她男友
- Who you texting, Debs? - Her boyfriend.
-闭嘴  卡尔  -你有男友了
- Shut up, Carl. - You have a boyfriend?
-我不是什么都得向你报告吧  -可你以前是
- I don't tell you everything. - You used to.
但我有点担心他其中一个睾丸还没降下来
But I am concerned that one of his testicles hasn't descended yet.
-什么  -你是个太监  利亚姆
- What? - Ha-ha, you're a eunuch, Liam.
之前没人告诉过你吗
Hasn't anyone told you this before?
没有  免费诊所的人基本不会说英语
No, they barely speak English at the free clinic,
这是我第一次享用医保  所以之前全不知情
and this is the first time I've had insurance, so no.
他都快三岁了
Well, he's almost three years old.
"小丸子"应该都降下来了才对
This puppy should have dropped by now.
跟我们说实话吧  医生
Be honest with us, doctor.
是因为他是黑人的缘故吗
Is it because he's black?
您别介意
You'll have to excuse him, okay?
进入青春期后  他就成了野蛮人
Puberty has turned him into a barbarian.
没错  谁叫他
Yeah, that's 'cause he masturbates
-一天在浴室撸十次管  -别吵了
- ten times a day in the bathroom. - Enough!
医生会觉得我们特别没教养的
This nice doctor is gonna think we live under a rock.
要是这个睾丸还不快点降下来
Well, if it doesn't drop soon,
他就得动手术了
he's gonna have to have surgery.
好了  卡尔  到你了
All right, Carl, you are next.
完事啦   完事啦  完事啦
All done, all done, all done, all done, all done.
好吧  让我先看看你的腋下
All right, let me see your pits.
都开始冒"嫩芽"了呢
Oh, you got a couple sprouts coming out, don't you?
下面也有不少  你要不要瞧瞧
Yeah, and I got some down below too--you wanna see?
我相信你没说谎
I'll take your word for it.
看来  你正在经历青春期的痛苦折磨呢
It sounds like you are going through the throes of puberty.
可不  随之而来的压力令我头疼
Yeah, and the stress is giving me headaches.
可能得给我开点奥施康定[止痛药]
Probably need some oxy.
别听他胡说
Oh, don't listen to him.
他是想给他爸爸开
He's trying to get it for his father.
他快死了
He's dying.
全是他自己一手造成的
His bed. He made it.
我的医保包含避孕药吗
Does my insurance cover the pill?
当然  自付五美金就行
It sure does. Co-pay is $5.
那太好了
Oh, wow, that's great.
可比在计生组排队两小时队强多了
Beats waiting in line at planned parenthood for two hours.
我也想开始吃避孕药
I want to go on the pill too.
什么  不行
What? No.
你月经都还没来呢
You haven't even gotten your period yet.
-唐娜·多蒂月经来了  -什么  她才九岁
- Donna Doty got her period. - What? She's nine!
人家已经用上卫生巾了
And she's riding the cotton pony.
太不公平了
Ugh, this isn't fair!
这是你的处方药单
Uh, here's your prescription for ortho.
-谢谢  -既然你都提到了
- Thanks. - While you got that thing out,
-能不能顺便开点止痛药  -抱歉  孩子
- a few pain meds? - Sorry, buddy.
太不公平了
Ugh, this isn't fair!
欢迎来到青少年的精彩世界
Welcome to the wonderful world of teenagers.
我知道你有阴谋  说英语的  我加注
I see your muffin, English, and raise you.
好吧  老天  我也加注
Okay, okay, Jesus! I raise you.
该死  我不跟
Oh, shit, I fold.
-我跟  -我也跟
- I call. - Call.
-好了  摊牌吧  -一起
- Okay, show. - Let's go.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
-祝你下次好运  -别在意
- Hey, better luck next time. - It's okay.
我15分钟后有个随堂测验
Oh, I got a quiz in 15 minutes.
得留点儿时间学习
Need time to study.
-15分钟  -我就是这作风  老兄
- 15 minutes? - I'm just doing me, amigo.
-好吧  伙计  -回见
- All right, man. - See ya.
-回见  -回见  各位
- See ya. - See you, guys.
仁慈的上帝啊
For the love of jesus!
第10题  下列哪一项会引起
Question ten, which of the following could cause
通胀率和失业率同时增长
simultaneous increases in inflation and unemployment?
"A"  政府减少开支
"A," a decrease in government spending,
"B"  货币供应量减少
"B," a decrease in money supply,
C  货币流通速度下降
"C," a decrease in the velocity of money,
还是D  通胀预期增加
or "D," an increase in inflationary expectations?
-D  -谁回答的D
- "D." - who said "D"?
你们答对了
You got it.
把卷子传回给本人
Pass the quizzes back to the person they belong to.
-真抱歉  -60分
- Sorry. - Oh, 60?
还行吧  我是说  换算一下的话
That's not bad-- I mean, with the curve,
就相当于是B+了  对吧
it's probably like a B+, right?
-哪国的算法  -好了  安静下来
- In what country? - All right, settle down.
你复习了吗
Did you study for it?
课前复习了几分钟
Yeah, a few minutes before class.
我熬了一整夜
I was up all night.
很显然  你的复习方法更优
Obviously, your system worked better than mine.
如果想要额外的分数
If anyone wants extra credit,
我建议你们花点时间
I suggest you spend some time
去找我的辅导教师  做些练习题
answering practice questions with my tutor.
好了  哪些同学提前读完了第七章
Okay, who has read ahead to Chapter 7?
好了  谁能告诉我  扩大政府财政赤字
All right, who can tell me if a large government
会使国民储蓄增加还是减少
budget deficit raises or lowers the national saving?
-减少  -很好
- Lowers. - Exactly.
好了  下列说法正确的是...
All right, now evaluate the following statement...
上次清洗这些杯子是什么时候
When was the last time these things were cleaned?
四月份  给你  艾伦
April. Here you go, Alan.
冠军早餐
Breakfast of champions.
需要的话  还有橙汁
And some OJ if you'd like.
但估计不太新鲜了
Yeah, I wouldn't count on that expiration date, though.
在这里橙汁很少派上用场
Not much use of orange juice in this place.
我真的不用
Really, I'm good.
我爸老了挺丑的  对吧
Dad didn't age very well, did he?
这些照片是六十岁的时候拍的
And he was in his 60s in those pictures.
你该看看八十岁的
You should've seen him in his 80s.
逝者已逝
Hey, man's dead.
-你们尊重一下  -不  没关系
- Have some respect. - No, no, it's fine.
你们肯定知道  我和我爸  关系不太好
He and I, I'm sure you know, didn't get along very well.
跟你说实话
You know, to be honest with you,
我都不知道有你这么个人
I didn't even know you existed.
他只说过  有个女儿
He only mentioned having a daughter.
说的就是我
That would be me.
准备好了的话  我们可以开始了
When you're ready, we can begin.
我有一份斯坦利的遗嘱  要读给你们听
I have Stanley's will here, which I'd like to read to you.
但出于尊重
Um, but out of respect, you know,
我会略过一些污秽的用词
I'll skip some of the colorful language.
不用  直接读原稿
Oh, no. Please, go ahead, read it.
我确定以前都听他讲过
I'm sure we've all heard it before.
本人  斯坦利·温斯顿·柯普切克
Uh, I, Stanley Winston Kopchek,
在身心均健康的状态下
being of sound mind and body,
愿将我的枪支收藏留给我
leave to my sniveling, faggoty,
"娘们儿唧唧的鼻涕虫
fag of a fagorama daughter
基妈生的伪娘儿子"
by the name of Alan Willard Kopchek
艾伦·维拉德·柯普切克
my gun collection,
希望在她舔下一个艾滋病鸡巴之前
in the hopes that she'll kill herself
一枪崩了自己
before she chugs another aids cock.
以前好像没听过吧
Not sure we all heard that before.
对于我希望是自己亲生儿子的人
And to the man who I wished had been born my son,
凯文·鲍尔
Kevin Ball,
我把我珍爱的艾莱伯酒吧留给他
I leave my beloved Alibi Room.
-什么  -天呐
- What? - Oh, my.
我知道不会有什么好事  但没想到竟然...
I knew it would be bad. I didn't know it would be that--
艾伦  对不起  我全不知情
Alan, I'm sorry. I had no idea.
-我要质疑遗嘱  -必须的  你应该这么做
- I'll contest the will. - Absolutely, you should.
他写遗嘱的时候可能喝多了
He was probably drunk when he wrote it.
一些都是按合理程序走的
Everything was done by the book.
这样吧  也别折腾了
You know what? Never mind.
酒吧给凯文吧
Let kevin have the bar.
艾伦  你确定吗  这不太公平
Alan, are you-- are you sure? That doesn't seem fair.
得了  你觉得来喝酒的恐同份子
Oh, come on, do you think the homophobes
会承认我是这里的老板吗
that come in this place are gonna take to me as the owner?
你可以卖掉
You could always sell it.
好吧  我们这么做
Okay, tell you what we'll do.
凯文
Kevin,
两年期  年你每月给我500美金
why don't you send me $500 a month for two years,
这破地方
about what I would've gotten
也就能卖这些钱了
If I had sold this shit hole?
好的
Okay.
我来起草文件
So I'll--I'll write up the paperwork.
会给你们一人一份副本
I'll get you both a copy then.
很好  艾伦  谢谢你
That sounds fair. Alan, thank you.
我保证  我会发扬斯坦的遗志
I-I promise, I will uphold Stan's legacy.
好的一面
The good stuff,
不是那些"娘们儿  基佬  艾滋病鸡巴"之类的
not all that "faggoty, fag, aids cock" stuff.
介意我把我爸带走吗
Do you mind if I take dad?
当然不
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
-早  菲奥娜  -嗨  吉娜
- Morning, Fiona. - Hi, Gena.
有机会  你该跟我们一起练瑜伽
You know, you should join us for yoga sometime.
能精神充沛一整天
It's a good way to start the day.
我刚适应有医保的日子
Yeah, I'm just getting used to having health insurance.
还没做好去健身的准备
Not sure I can handle the gym just yet.
好的
All right.
有人在吗
Knock, knock.
你找我  先生
You wanted to see me, sir?
是的  昨晚没什么事吧
Yeah. Everything okay last night?
没有  怎么了
Yeah, why?
我不知道
Eh, I don't know.
你说你会给我打电话  然后来我家
You said you'd call and come over.
没有我你寂寞了吗
Aw, were you lonely without me?
我觉得你可能是害怕我下双陆棋时
Well, I figured you might be a little afraid
再次把你杀得落花流水
that I would kick your ass in strip backgammon again.
你倒是想杀得我落花流水
Uh, you wish you could kick my ass in strip backgammon.
你是在跟我宣战吗
Are you throwing the gauntlet down right now?
随时奉陪  放马过来
Yeah, anytime. Bring it on.
好的  就这么定了
Okay, you got it.
关于昨晚
Hey, about last night--
你因为这事儿要见我吗
Is this why you wanted to see me?
不不  事实上  我想见你
No, no, no, actually, I wanted to see you
是因为我想让你去外面跑跑
because I have decided to put you out in the field.
放牛吗
Like a cow?
就是放牛
Exactly like a cow.
今天我要给你指派三个销售项目回访
I have three sales calls that I am sending you on today.
第一个是热狗店
The first one, the Dog House,
然后是里维埃拉剧院  最后是林肯体育馆
then the Riviera Theater, and then the Lincoln Arena,
-伊利诺伊州滑翔者队比赛的地方  -好的
- where the Illinois Gliders play. - Okay.
因为沃利再过几个月就要退休了
So, you know, since Wally's retiring in, what,
我觉得  让他的客户见一见
a couple of months, I thought it'd be a good idea
他们新的销售代表是个好主意
for his clients to meet their new sales rep.
我吗
Me?
如果他们喜欢你的话
Well, if they like you, yeah.
那秀一秀乳沟没坏处吧
I take it boobs wouldn't hurt?
是吧  他们跟沃利打了十六年交道
Yeah, they've been dealing with Wally for the past 16 years.
是呀
Yeah.
所以露一露大长腿也行
So legs would be good too.
以男朋友的立场来说  我不同意
As your boyfriend, I say no.
以老板的立场来说  放马去吧
As your boss, oh, hell, yeah.
对了  让马里奥给你安排辆车
Oh, oh, oh, hey, have Mario hook you up with a company car.
真的假的  还有车开
Really? A car?
当然了  你打算搭轻轨过去吗
Yeah, a car. Did you expect to take the EL?
没有啊
I-I guess not.
你有驾照  对吧
You have a license, right?
当然有
Sure. Of course.
利普  等一等
Hey, Lip, wait.
阿曼达姐妹会待会儿要开个派对
Amanda's sorority's having a happy hour later.
你看起来需要放松一下
Thought you could use a pick-me-up.
谢啦
Thanks.
好啦 宝贝
All right, baby.
我快打扫干净了
I'm all finished up.
有什么话想对他的骨灰说吗
You want to say something over the ashes?
这主意不错
That's a good idea.
斯坦  你这个老混蛋
Stan, you son of a bitch,
你告诉我要成为一个真男人  他得深爱过女人
you taught me that a man isn't a man unless he's loved a woman,
生吃过山羊心脏
eaten the heart out of a live goat,
或者把一个德国兵的脸撕烂
or ripped a german soldier's face off.
起码  第一项我做得还不错
One out of three ain't bad.
能成为你的养子我很荣幸
I'm proud to call you my foster pop.
我会想你的  老爸
I'm gonna miss you, old man.
说得好  宝贝
Nice, baby.
好啦  我要把他丢出去了
All right, I'm gonna take him outside,
然后再回家睡一觉
and then I'm gonna go home and take a nap.
有点不舒服
I'm not feeling so good.
-你怎么了  -还不是孩子闹的
- What's wrong? - The baby,
再加上吸入了斯坦的骨灰  更难受了
and I'm sure inhaling Stan's dna didn't help.
这酒吧来的真及时
Hey, good timing, you getting this bar
马上要有两个孩子了对吧
when you're about to have two babies, huh?
可不是吗  现在我终于能负担得起
Yeah, no shit, now I can afford
卡罗天天念叨的那些乱七八糟的母婴用品了
all that ridiculous maternity crap carol keeps bitching about.
小维也终于可以不再为钱操心了
And V can stop worrying about money.
当然啦
Damn straight.
孩子他爸会照顾好我的
My baby daddy can take care of me!
还有你的孩子和你妈的孩子
And your baby and your mama's baby.
我们真是个前卫的家庭  宝贝
We're a regular modern family, baby.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
你好 小维
Hey, V.
拜拜  小维
Bye, V.
凯特  猜猜你的新老板是谁
Guess who's your new boss, Kate.
她说什么呢
What she talking about?
现在我怎么说你就得怎么做
You gotta do everything I say now.
斯坦把酒吧留给我了
Stan gave me the bar.
你怎么会想要它
Why would you want it?
没看最近的账目吗
Have you looked at the books lately?
痒死了
So itchy.
擦
Fuck.
弗兰克
Hey, Frank.
你从儿科医生那里弄到什么好货没有
Did you get me anything from the pediatrician?
没  菲奥娜不让我拿
No, Fiona wouldn't let me.
老天呐
Christ.
但我想到一个办法  可以在上数学课时
But I figured a way to rub one out at my desk
悄悄在下面撸一管  而不会被人发现
in the middle of math class without anyone noticing.
儿子你最赞
That's real good, son.
坐后排的好处  对吧
Benefits of sitting in the back, right?
没错
Yeah.
什么味道
What's that smell?
是我
Me.
-什么  -我的肝终于要不行了
- What? - My liver's finally giving up.
要我去杂货店帮你偷一个回来吗
Want me to steal you one from the grocery store?
没那么简单
Not that easy.
-我的肝正在在体内腐烂  -你怎么知道
-Mine is rotting inside my body. - How do you know?
看到我胸口上蜘蛛网状的血管了吗
You see these spider veins on my chest?
我的眼睛估计也充血了吧
And my eyes are-- are probably bloodshot, right?
再看看这个
Look at this.
好恶  巨粗的脚脖子
Ew, cankles.
像个裹着破布的水肿少年曲棍球手
Like a teenage lacrosse player on the rag, retaining water.
那我们该怎么办
What do we do?
没办法  除非有人愿意捐肝给我
Nothing we can do unless somebody wants to give me their liver.
谁会愿意
Who?
死人
A dead guy.
处理掉
Get rid of it.
不不不  不是
No, no, no, no.
倒掉  就像刚才那罐尿一样
Out the window with the gatorade pee.
反正早晚也会变成那个
Gonna wind up there anyway.
我只是省去它中间变化的过程罢了
I'm just cutting out the middleman.
别再弄酒了  我要药  什么都行
No more alcohol, just drugs, whatever you can get me.
我去弄吗
Me?
一个垂死之人凭自己的意志是戒不了酒的
A dying man can't be expected to wean himself off booze by himself.
你想要什么药
What do you want?
随便什么都行  大麻  止痛片
Whatever you can get. Pot, percocet--
-吗啡  -安定
- Morphine? - Valium.
-镇静剂  -维柯丁
- Ativan? - Vicodin.
非那根
Sizzurp?
我一直都想试试那个
I always wanted to try that.
包在我身上
I'm on it.
你是我的骄傲  儿子
I'm proud of you, son.
我不会让你失望的  老爸
Won't let you down, dad.
我的天
O.M.G.
我可以把我的孩子打扮成粉色的羊羔
I can dress my baby like a pink lamb.
我最好生的是女孩
I better have a girl and not a stupid boy.
不  你该去把它打掉
No, you better abort that thing.
-太晚啦  -人流永远不嫌晚
- Too late. - Never too late.
马蒂邀请我晚些时候去他家
Matty invited me over to his apartment later.
-他爸妈在家吗  -他没说
- His parents gonna be home? - Didn't say.
那肯定不在了  这也代表他想嘿咻了
Bet they're not, which means he'll want to do it.
最好带上避孕套
Here, better bring a condom.
我总是忘记
I always forget to do that.
如果他是个有风度的男生  钱包里会有套套
If he's a classy guy, he'll have a condom in his wallet.
没错
Totes.
看  我还能把孩子打扮成艺妓呢
Look, I can dress my baby like a geisha girl.
我觉得  我还没做好破处的准备
I'm not sure I'm ready to have sex.
当下就是最完美的时刻
Right now is the perfect time.
还没开始来月经  就不会怀孕
If you don't bleed, then you can't breed.
月经到底什么时候才会来
When am I gonna get my period?
唐娜·多蒂都来了  她才九岁
Donna Doty got hers, and she's nine.
我听说唐娜连狗的鸡巴都舔
I heard donna Doty blows dogs.
这上面说有些女人到25岁才来月经
It says here some women don't menstruate till they're 25
原因是饮用水中含有化学成分
due to the chemicals in our water.
那也太爽了吧  如果卵巢被感染了的话
That'd be sweet-- if your ovaries are polluted,
可以不戴套套操到一把年纪呢
then you can screw without protection till you're old.
可是我们才刚认识
But we're just getting to know each other.
我都还没告诉他我的年龄
I haven't even told him how old I am yet.
别告诉他
Don't.
他如果发现你才十三岁  一定会甩了你
He'll dump you if he finds out you're 13.
嘴巴闭紧  装得好像十六岁一样
Keep your mouth shut, and act like you're 16.
-怎么装  -多舔舔嘴唇
- How? - Lick your lips a lot.
他会认为你想给他吹箫
He'll think you're gonna blow him.
-你给他吹过吗  -我觉得没有
- Have you yet? - I-I don't think so.
很好  等等
Good. Wait.
先让他给你买些东西
Make him buy you something first.
比如什么
Like what?
我也不知道  衣服  首饰  iPad什么的
I don't know, clothes, jewelry, an ipad.
一些市区服装店的衣服
Something from urban outfitters.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
你总是关在厕所里撸  真恶心
You're always in there. It's disgusting.
你看什么看  傻逼
What are you looking at, fucktard?
只是为我待会儿的意淫取材而已
Just making a mental image for my spank bank later.
0.2英里之后请左转
Turn left in 2/10 of a mile.
你开车上路没问题吧
Hey, you get in the car and on the road okay?
一切都好  这车还有暖气呢
Yeah, all good. This thing has heat.
你没告诉我我每天还有免费午餐呢
And you didn't tell me I get a meal per diem.
生活还能比这更美好吗
How could life get any better?
我很高兴你过得开心
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
你介意我带上男友帽  暂时转变成男友角色吗
You mind if I put my boyfriend hat on for just a second?
只要身上没穿别的就行
As long as you're not wearing anything else.
什么都没有
Nope.
一丝不挂地站在装载区
Just standing here on the loading dock totally naked.
不  其实我是想接着聊完早上的话题
No, I wanted to finish our conversation from this morning, actually.
下双陆棋时我把你杀得落花流水的事吗
About me kicking your ass in backgammon?
关于你说昨晚会给我打电话的事
Oh, about you saying you were gonna call last night.
天呐  真的假的
Oh, my god. Really?
听着  没接到你的电话  让我很担心
Look, I worried about you when I didn't hear from you.
你可以打给我啊
You could've called me.
是的  但那不是重点
Yeah, but that's not the point.
那重点是什么
What is the point?
就是你说过  你会打给我
That you said you were gonna call.
前方500英尺就是您的目的地
You will reach your destination in 500 feet.
我得停车了  快到体育馆了
I gotta go. I'm almost at the arena.
好吧  去搞定他们
Okay, cool. Yeah, go get 'em.
我们可以晚些时候再谈
Uh, we can finish this later.
嘿  你也是来上辅导课的吗
Hey, you, uh-you here for the tutoring?
是啊  不过前面一个班还没下课
Yup, the earlier session's still in there, though.
-我叫雪莉  -我叫利普
- I'm Shelly. - Uh, Lip.
有意思  那是什么名字的简称
Interesting. What's it stand for?
利普施瓦茨或者菲利普  你选吧
Lipschwitz or Phillip, your choice.
我喜欢利普施瓦茨
Oh. I like Lipschwitz.
那我就是利普施瓦茨
Then that's who I am.
你是不会使用宏吗
So are you having trouble with Macro?
不  其实不是
No, no, not really.
我  我根本不在乎那玩意儿
I just--I don't give a shit about it.
为什么
Why not?
我不知道  你真的认为
I don't know, I mean, you really think
那玩意儿在现实世界中能帮到我们吗
it's something that is gonna help us out in the real world?
所以你没打算进美联储工作  对吧
Oh, so you're not planning on running the Federal Reserve, huh?
-你会吗  -或许吧
- Are you? - Maybe.
我觉得可能不会
I don't know. I doubt I will.
那你在这里干什么
So why are you here, then?
我是来说服辅导老师给我一些额外的分数
I'm here to talk the tutor into giving me some extra credit points.
然后就走人
Then I'm gonna split.
我希望你能成功
Well, I hope that works out for you.
一向成功
Always does.
教室归你了  雪莉
All yours, Shells bells.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不进来吗   利普施瓦茨
You coming in, Lipschwitz?
该死  你就是那个辅导老师  对吧
Shit, you're, uh-you're the tutor, huh?
看看你能不能说服我多给一些分数
Let's see if you can talk me into giving you extra credit.
你确定菲奥娜说这样没关系吗
You sure Fiona said it was okay?
她想帮助弗兰克  现在他戒酒了
She wants to help Frank now that he's not drinking anymore.
所以你有什么可以给我
So what you got for me?
你再敢吵醒我睡午觉
I got a punch in your face
我就朝你脸上揍一拳
If you ever wake me up from my nap again.
我操
Holy crap!
我是个护士
I'm a nurse.
不  你是帮老年人倒夜壶的
No, you empty bedpans for old people.
我是个贫民区护士  让人们到我这儿来
I'm a ghetto nurse-better for folks around here
总比去急诊室排十八个小时的队要好
to come to me than to wait 18 hours in the emergency room.
止痛片  应该能行了
Percocet, that should do it.
别急  小家伙  我先给菲奥娜打个电话
Not so quick, sparky. Let me call Fiona first.
别这样  我们击个掌  我就告辞了
Come on, just give me five, and we'll call it a day.
瞧吧   我就知道你在说谎
See, I knew you were lying.
至少我没有私藏满满一柜的药
At least I don't have a cabinet filled with drugs.
你从哪里弄来的  老家伙那里偷的吗
Where'd you get that stuff-steal it from the geriatrics?
你管我从哪里弄来的
I got it from mind-your-business town.
天呐  今天你可真暴躁
Jeez, you're crabby today.
我感觉不太舒服
I don't feel good.
所以你的屁股上才渗血吗
Is that why you got blood on your ass?
什么
What?
你怎么不早点告诉我
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
糟了
Oh, shit.
我出血了
I'm spotting.
我们必须赶去医院  孩子可能保不住了
We gotta go to the hospital. I might be losing the baby.
快啊
Come on.
那是什么意思
And what does this mean?
斯坦从2007年开始就没让我缴工资税了
Stan hasn't let me send in his payroll taxes since 2007.
老天爷啊
Oh, dear lord.
我猜那肯定不是因为他没有欠税
And I'm assuming it's not because he didn't owe any.
你猜得很对
You're assuming right.
同时  他从2010年开始就没更新过营业执照
He also hasn't renewed his business license since 2010.
酒吧每个月营收入有多少
How much does the bar make every month?
在减掉员工工资  杂费  营业税后
Well, after paying us, the utilities, payroll taxes,
生意好的月份可以赚1300块  喂
Maybe $1,300 in a good month. Hello.
好了  不准再吃了
All right, that's it, no more.
从现在开始  嗑坚果也要付钱
From now on, everybody has to pay for their nuts.
说到为坚果付钱[睾丸]
Hey, speaking of paying for nuts,
我昨晚在米奇老婆的手里消费了一炮
I dumped my load in Mickey's wife's hand last night.
-功夫不赖  -小凯
- Not bad. - Kev.
是菲奥娜家的孩子  卡尔
It's Fiona's kid, Carl.
说什么小维和他一起去了急诊室
Something about V and him going to the emergency room.
喂
Hello?
真不敢相信  在芝加哥长大的我
I can't believe I've grown up in Chicago
从没来过这里
and I've never been here.
这里可以容纳多少观众
How many fans does this place seat?
一场比赛16000名
16,000 for a game.
太巨大了
Giant.
-大约有多少人会买啤酒  -九成会买吧
- What percentage buys beer? - About 90, I bet.
那就是每场比赛会消耗14000个杯子
So about 14,000 cups a game?
我估计  至少有1/3的杯子会被带离体育馆
And I'll bet at least 1/3 of those cups are leaving the arena.
估计得差不多
That's about right.
如果纸杯上面印有伊利诺斯州滑翔机队商标
So if those cups had the Illinois Gliders logo on them
而不只是普通的杯子
instead of just being plain cups,
这样的话  就有5000个杯子
What is that, like, 5,000 pieces of free advertising
在免费做广告宣传
just walking around out there?
亲爱的  你这是在推销吗
Are you trying to upsell me, sweetheart?
只是想多了解一下你这里的生意嘛  伦纳德
I'm just trying to learn more about your business, Leonard.
麦克跟我说这次只是见个面随便聊聊
And Mike said this was just a friendly meet and greet.
我们见面了  聊得也很开心不是吗
And am absolutely enjoying meeting and greeting you.
不如你领我去看看售卖区怎么样
Why don't you show me the concession stands?
你们卖不卖巧克力面圈
Do you guys have churros?
-我很想吃那个  -巧克力面圈
- I love me a churro. - Churros, churros, churros.
你笑什么
What's so amusing?
绝对不是笑这本书里的东西
Oh, uh, definitely nothing in this book.
你在第七章学到什么了吗
Did you learn anything in Chapter seven?
是的  信用低的穷人也是可以拿到贷款的
Yes, uh, poor people with bad credit can still get a mortgage.
-那个贷款叫什么  -次级房贷
- What's that mortgage called? - Subprime.
对了  你要不要跟我去参加个派对
Hey, do you want to go to a party with me
就今天下午
this afternoon?
你认真起来  还是挺有效果的嘛
Look what happens when he actually reads the textbook.
-学到了知识呢  -是啊
- He learns something. - Sure, yeah.
可是这些没用的知识网上一搜就有
Useless information I could just find on the internet,
你还没回答我的问题
but it doesn't answer my question.
可那些没用的知识
Well, that useless information
刚帮你拿到了10分
just got you ten extra credit points.
-能不能加到15  -再见
- Do you want to make it 15? - Good-bye.
派对我之前就决定去了  那是我的姐妹会
And I'm already going to the party--it's my sorority.
如果你死了  能把肝脏给弗兰克吗
If you die, can Frank have your liver?
我不会死的
I'm not gonna die.
如果我拿枕头闷死你呢
You would if I shoved a pillow over your head.
你在这儿啊  怎么了
Oh, there you are. What is going on?
我能走了吗
Can I leave now?
你难道不想知道我到底怎么了吗
Don't you want to wait and find out what's wrong with me?
走吧
Go.
-怎么了  -我轻微出血了
- What happened? - I started spotting.
怪不得我今天觉得不舒服
Must be why I wasn't feeling so hot today.
-孩子怎么样  -还在等检查结果
- How's the baby? - We're waiting for labs.
医生出去找超声波仪了
The doctor's out looking for an ultrasound machine now.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
这破医院穷到配不起几台超声波仪吗
They can't afford a fucking ultrasound machine in every room?
真他妈搞笑
This is some bullshit.
-有人吗  人都哪去了  -小凯
- Excuse me. Excuse me! - Kev.
干什么
What?
抱抱我好吗
I need a hug.
宝贝
Baby.
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
-我需要肝脏  -你的肝脏怎么了
- I need a liver. - What's wrong with yours?
是给我爸爸的  他的肝脏腐烂了
It's for my father. His is rotting.
-还有怪味  -天呐  情况很严重啊
- It smells. - Oh, my, that ain't good.
他在受捐赠名单上吗
Is he on the donor list?
应该不在  能给他报名吗
I don't think so. Can I sign him up?
需要请专业人士帮他检查
Your father would have to be seen by a specialist,
然后告诉我们  才能上名单
then referred to us, so he can be put on the list.
然后就有肝脏了吗
Then he gets a liver?
需要等别人捐赠给他
He'd have to wait for one to be available.
要等多久
How long does that take?
小朋友  美国有17000人
Sweetie, more than 17,000 people in the U.S.
都在肝脏移植名单上
are on the liver transplant list.
那你们肯定需要很多肝脏
That's a lot of dead livers you're gonna need.
每年有6000人有幸能等到合适的肝脏
6,000 people are fortunate enough to get one each year.
那剩下的人呢
What about the rest?
并不是每个人都那么幸运
Doesn't work out for everyone.
如果器官捐献中心不能提供足够的器官
What's the point of being an organ donating center
那还有什么意义
if you're not donating enough organs?
你们家里的人可以为他捐一部分肝脏
Someone from your family can donate a portion of their liver.
我  用我的
Me. I'll do it.
需要年满十八周岁
You need to be over 18.
我哥哥和姐姐可以
My brother and my sister are.
这是个好开始  你可以看看
Well, that's a start. Why don't you find out
他们与你的父亲血型是否相符
if they're a blood match with your father?
肯定相符  我爸爸跟我妈在一起的时候
I already know they are-- my father only screwed
只上过一个墨西哥妓女
a mexican whore while he was with my mom,
她们不可能怀孕
and they can't get pregnant.
每个人的血型都不一样
Everyone's blood type is different,
有血缘关系也可能血型不同
Sometimes even if they're related.
给你这些便携测量工具
Take these at-home testing kits.
扎破手指
Prick the person's finger,
然后把血滴在里面的卡片上
put a drop of blood on the enclosed card.
卡上会显示血型
It'll show their blood type.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
搞定了  抱歉拖了这么久
Okey dokey. Sorry about the delay.
是什么情况
What's going on?
她会没事吗  孩子流产了吗
Is she okay? Did we lose the baby?
恰恰相反
Oh, on the contrary.
那她为什么出血
Well, why is she bleeding then?
你的检查结果出来了
Okay, we got your labs back.
你的雌激素  孕激素  生长激素水平都很高
Your estrogen, progesterone, and H.G.H. are through the roof,
因此造成了点状出血
which would explain the spotting.
我们来看看
All right, we'll take a look here.
点状出血现象很正常
Spotting, very common
尤其是怀了多胞胎之后
with implantation of multiple fetuses.
-多什么  -多胞胎
- Fetu-whos? - Multiple?
是啊  你们看
Yeah, take a look.
双胞胎
Two babies?
不对  有三个呢
Nope, mm, three.
-恭喜你  -三个
- Congratulations. - Three?
看你这个反应  似乎没这个打算
I take it from your reaction you weren't planning this.
没这个打算  谁他妈会想要三个孩子啊
Planning this? Who the fuck plans three babies?
请尽快跟产科医师安排一下会面
You need to make an appointment as soon as possible with your O.B.
产科医师  我直接约兽医见面吧
O.B.? I need to make an appointment with the vet.
我他妈都要生一窝了
I'm having a damn litter!
宝贝  你知道这意味着什么吗
Baby, you know what this means?
我的老二太牛逼了
I got a magic dick.
出去的时候把这张表带给前台
Take this form up to the front desk on your way out,
祝你们好运
and good luck.
我都不知道该吓尿
I don't know whether to freak out
还是去给大家展示我的神老二
or thrust my almighty dick in everyone's face!
你还是吓尿吧  我都要生三胞胎了
You need to be freaking out. I'm having triplets!
三胞胎  三胞胎
Triplets! Triplets!
我的老二可牛逼了  兄弟  简直碉堡了
I got a magic penis, man. I got a magic penis!
-你他妈能不能闭嘴  -我的老二可牛逼了
- Would you shut the fuck up? - I got a magic penis.
你不是又要谈我昨晚没打电话的事吧
I hope this isn't about me not calling you last night again.
不  是其他事
Uh, no. Actually, it's not.
那些客户非常喜欢你
It's about the clients loving you.
他们今天都给我回复了
I heard back from all of them today.
快说  他们怎么说的
Ah, do tell. What'd they say?
你还记得滑翔机体育馆的伦纳德吗
Well, you remember Leonard from the Gliders?
谢谢
Thanks.
之前你们谈过的  印有标识的纪念杯
He wants to order those souvenir logo cups
他想下一批订单
that you guys talked about.
-太好了  -确实不错
- Sweet. - Yeah, that is sweet.
你不必过去销售杯子的
You know, you didn't have to go down there and sell them.
我就想让你打个招呼
I just wanted you to say hi.
我到了那儿
Yeah, well, when I got there,
觉得不把握时机就太浪费了
it seemed like a waste not to seize the moment.
听听你说的话啊
Whoa, listen to you.
我就喜欢我的销售姑娘有这种冲劲
That's the kind of initiative I like from my sales girls.
赴汤蹈火让老板高兴嘛
Mm, anything to please the boss.
现在我是想谈谈你昨晚没打给我的事了
Ok, so now I do want to talk about  you not calling me last night.
-天呐  不要啊  -好吧
- Oh, dear lord, no! - All right, all right.
我这样是因为我关心你
Listen, it's because I care about you, okay?
我想彼此间建立信任
I want to build trust with each other.
你因为我没打给你而不信任我
You don't trust me because I didn't call?
不不  我的意思是
Well, no, no, no, no. I mean, you know, I--
我的前女友一直骗我
My ex was always lying to me.
我的前男友也是呢
Yeah, so was mine.
那既然答应了就打给我
Then just call when you say you're gonna.
-好吗  -好吧  抱歉
- Okay? - All right, I'm sorry.
别按了  傻逼
Get off my ass, dick face!
天呐  我就当你在跟另一辆车说了
Jesus, I'm gonna assume that was directed at another car.
傻逼都贴到我保险杆上来了
Fuckwad is riding my bumper.
卡尔打来电话了
Uh-- and Carl's on the other line.
我得挂了  回头打给你
I got to go. I'll call you back.
也许不会  我也不知道  拜
Or not, I don't know. Bye.
卡尔  什么事
Carl, what's going on?
-你什么血型的  -怎么了  你受伤了吗
- What's your blood type? - Why, are you hurt?
好消息  你和利普都能把肝捐给弗兰克
Good news, you and Lip can both donate your liver to Frank.
卡尔  拜托你别再担心弗兰克了
Ugh, Carl, please, please stop worrying about Frank.
他就是无止境的黑洞
He is a black hole of endless need
会把你整个人都吸干
that will suck the life out of you.
他的肝烂了  身上一股猴笼的味道
His liver is rotting. He smells like a monkey cage.
那纯粹是他自找的
Well, he made his choices.
你得帮帮他
You have to help him.
-不  我不用  -好吧
- No, I don't. - Fine.
天呐
Jesus!
贱人
Bitch!
-操你妈  你个臭傻逼  -臭婊子
- Oh, fuck you, you fucking asshole! - Fucking cunt!
至少我没有微缩的鸡巴
At least I don't have a tiny penis!
你个混蛋  我差点撞到你的车
You piece of shit! I almost hit your car!
操  惨了
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
妈的  倒车  快倒车
Oh, shit. Back up, back up!
快倒车啊  快点
Back up, back up, back up,
倒车
back!
操
Oh, shit!
不要  天呐
No! Oh, my God!
住手  别
Stop it, no!
倒车
Back up!
后退
婊子
Bitch!
我说我讨厌她
I told her I hate her.
恶心的中等平均数
Gross medium average.
-你好啊  -抱歉迟到了
- What up? - Hey, sorry I'm late.
没关系  没有你派对一样进行
No, it's cool. The party went on without you.
-不可能  -这位是...
- That's impossible. - Hey, this is--
我之前叫你什么来着
What was it that I was calling you earlier?
-瑞普施瓦茨  -利普施瓦茨
- Ripschwitz? - Uh, Lipschwitz.
不过现在我们熟了
Um, but you've entered the inner circle now.
-叫我利普就行  -好吧  利普
- You can call me Lip. - Okay, Lip.
这就是你的姐妹会
So this is your sorority?
是啊  不过我没多大兴趣
Yeah. I'm not super into it, though.
我也不住在这里
I don't live in the house or anything.
好吧  那你有自己的住处
Okay. So--so you got your own place?
对  就在大学路
Mm-hmm, just off University Road.
改天我想去参观一下
I'd like to see that sometime.
-你肯定想  -你想喝什么
- I bet you would. - Hey, what are you drinking?
要我帮你弄点什么吗
You want me to get you something?
好啊  帮我弄到他
Uh, yeah. I would like you to get me that.
他在修热电学博士学位
He's working on his phd in thermo.
我不敢跟他说话
I'm terrified to talk to him.
你和我这就分手了吗
You and I breaking up?
你很可爱  但我是你老师
Oh, you're cute, but I'm your tutor.
所以呢
So?
感觉我像你保姆一样
That's like me being your babysitter.
我要跟查理·沃茨说什么
Now what do I say to Charlie Watts?
说你要带我去你在大学路的公寓
That you're gonna show me your apartment off University Road.
你倒想  拜托
You wish. Come on.
跟他调调情吧
Uh, just go flirt with him.
怎么调
How?
像对我那样
Like you're doing with me.
你是大一新生  很简单
You're a freshman. It's easy.
但我像大二学生一样会操
Yeah, but I fuck like a sophomore.
还是没戏
Still not happening.
你得帮帮我  我可给你加分了
You have to help me. I gave you extra credit.
好吧  夸夸他
Okay, fine, um... You know, give him shit.
男生就喜欢被夸
Guys like it when you give us shit.
夸什么
Shit about what?
就从那件1994年的格子花呢衬衫开始吧
Well, you start with that plaid shirt from 1994.
别这么说我的查理
Don't you talk about my Charlie that way.
快去吧  他会爱死你的  去吧
Yeah, just go. Go, go, he's gonna love you. Go.
如果他不喜欢你
You know, but if he doesn't,
这儿还有条大一的鸡巴等着你呢
there's freshman cock right here, waiting for you.
等它变成研究生鸡巴再打给我
Call me when it's grad school cock.
好吧
Okay.
小混蛋
Hey, douchebag.
-你什么血型的  -我也想你
- What's your blood type? - Um, I miss you too.
我能去你那儿测一下吗
Can I come up there and test it?
我记得在十年纪生物课上测过
I think we--we did it in, like, tenth grade bio class.
我是AB阳性  怎么了
AB positive. Why?
好了  我得挂了  拜
All right, gotta go. Bye.
等下啊  别挂
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait. Hold on.
你为什么问我这个
What do you want to know for?
你会跟菲奥娜一样生气的
You'll just get mad at me like Fiona did.
-我要挂了  -好吧  别挂
- I gotta go. - Okay, wait, wait, hold on.
你要不想谈  那就不谈  好吗
Look, we don't have to talk about it if you don't want to, okay?
告诉我家里其他事吧
You know, just tell me what else is going on.
-爸爸快死了  -好吧  别胡扯
- Dad's dying. - Yeah, no shit.
-怎么就没人在乎  -利亚姆的皮疹怎么样
- Why doesn't anyone care? - Hey, look, how's liam's rash?
-医生说是湿疹  -好吧
- Doctor says it's eczema. - Oh, okay.
给他开什么药了
What are they giving him for it?
-弗兰克吗  -不  利亚姆
- Frank? - No, Liam.
乳膏  他需要一个肝
Cream. He needs a liver.
-利亚姆  -弗兰克
- Liam? - Frank.
我一点都不吃惊
Oh, yeah. No, I'm not surprised.
你们要乳霜的钱吗
Hey, listen, do you guys want any cash for the cream?
菲奥娜的新医保能付
Fiona's new insurance covered it.
-不错  -我到站了  挂了
- Nice. - I'm at my stop. I got to go.
弗兰克
Frank!
干嘛  我在哪
What? Where--where am I?
我死了吗  这是天堂吗
Am I dead? Is this heaven?
看我给你弄了什么来
Look what I got for you.
扑热息痛
Perckie cs.
儿子  老爸太为你骄傲了
Oh, son, I am so proud of you.
手指伸出来
Give me your finger.
是"扯我的手指头"
It's "pull my finger."
前面的人扯手指  后面的人放屁
没时间开放屁玩笑  说正事呢
No time for fart jokes. This is business now.
O型血
"O" positive.
-你去哪儿  -去给你找肝脏
- Where you going? - To get you a liver.
你好  你是那小子的姐姐是吧
Hey, you, you're, um--you're that kid's older sister, right?
你能说得再含蓄些吗
Oh, could you be a little more vague?
靠  对不起
Yeah, fuck. Sorry, um...
在林肯·格鲁夫高中时我跟他同级  不好意思
He wa--he was my year at Lincoln Grove. Sorry.
如果你说的是古斯  那就是了
If you're talking about Gus, then yes.
古斯  对  就是他
Gus. Yeah, gus.
就是古斯
Gus, that's right.
他从萧尼惩教中心出来了吗
Um, hey, hey, they let him out of Shawnee Correctional yet?
没有  他太蠢了  加刑了
No, he got time added for being an idiot.
-好吧  -利普
- Okay. - Lip!
伙计
Hey, man.
你是哪位
Who the hell are you?
利普
Uh, Lip.
利普·加拉格
Lip--Lip Gallagher.
住在华莱士大街
From Wallace Street.
没错  仅此一家
Yeah, the one and only.
猜对了  你来这儿干什么
That's right. Hey, what are you doing here?
兄弟会某个阔佬晚上想找个炮友  还是...
One of these rich frat boys need a date for the night, or--
不是  混蛋  我在这儿上学
No, you asshole. I go to school here.
-不是吧  真的  -真的
- Oh, shit, seriously? - Seriously.
你可不是我们那儿唯一的聪明蛋
Yeah, you're not the only smart fuck from the yards.
我们来了四个  加上你五个了
There are four of us here. I guess five now, including you.
靠  对不起  我不知道
Shit, sorry. I--you know, I didn't know.
-那我就不计较了  -好的
- Yeah, I will let it slide. - Okay.
那你怎么样  在这儿过得如何
So how's it going? How you doing in this place?
还不错
Yeah, not bad.
很好
That's good.
我大一糟透了
Yeah, I sucked ass my freshman year.
我花了三个学期才学完
It took me three semesters to catch up
我同学在高中就学完了的东西
to what my classmates learned in high school.
我们家乡的教育简直是坨屎
Unbelievable what a shitty education we got back home.
是啊  想不想一起去餐厅
Yeah, hey, you want to walk over to the cafeteria with me?
我准备和那儿的洗碗工抽点大麻
You know, I was gonna blaze up with one of the dishwashers.
什么
What?
今晚我本来要跟另外一个小妞玩玩儿的
You see, I was supposed to hook up with this other chick tonight,
但是人家甩了我
but then I got dissed.
所以我想也许  你懂得
So, um, I was thinking maybe, you know,
我们一起抽个爽  然后来一发
me and you, we could smoke a fatty, maybe bang one out?
你没开玩笑吧
Are you for real?
是啊  没错  你看  那是我室友
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. You see, that-- that's my roommate
还有他女朋友在那儿抽着呢
down there with his girlfriend, hitting the bong.
估计他们后半夜才能回来
You know, they're not gonna be back till, like, after midnight,
所以我们可以搞一搞
so we're--we're good.
你以为把以前那种小混混耍帅搞妞那一套
Wow, so you think that just because you were some hot shit back home
搬过来也能在这儿用上吗
that that hood rat attitude is gonna work here?
操  至于这么大反应吗
Fuck. Excuse me for living.
没想到你来了这儿
I didn't realize this place turned you
就变成了白雪公主了呢
into a fucking Disney princess.
滚你妈蛋
No, fuck you.
我上大学  就是为了想摆脱你这种人
You're the kind of guy I came to college to get away from.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
操我  干我
Fuck me. Fuck me!
-好  -操我
- Okay. - Fuck me!
正在干着呢
Thought that's what I was doing.
爽  爽  老天  爽死我了
Yes, yes. Lord, have mercy!
这是客户资料
Here's the client folders.
好  很好  再夸你一次
Oh, yes. Yeah, good job again.
谢谢你给我机会
Well, thanks for giving me a shot.
当然
Hey, of course.
公司的车挡风玻璃碎了
Oh, the windshield on the company car was cracked,
不过马里奥正在修
but Mario's fixing it.
碎了
Cracked?
-怎么碎的  -不知道
- From what? - I don't know.
也许是树枝  或是孩子弄碎的
A tree branch maybe, some kids.
我从体育场出来就成那样了
It was like that when I got out of the arena.
但是你打电话的时候却没有说
But you didn't say anything about it when we talked on the phone?
你一直在跟我谈没给你回电话那件事
You were too busy giving me shit for not calling you back.
我倒成坏蛋了是吗
What an asshole I am, huh?
还想着让我们的关系更进一步
Wanting to make our relationship closer.
太可笑了
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
好吧  这么着吧  我补偿你
All right, you know what? I'll make it up to you.
送你回家如何
How about I give you a ride home?
等我拿了东西就走
Just let me grab my stuff and we'll go?
很好
Great.
我爸是O型血
My dad's "O" positive.
那你哥哥和姐姐呢
What about your brother and sister?
-利普是AB型  -真遗憾
- Lip's AB. - Oh, that's too bad.
那你姐姐呢
And your sister?
她不让我验血
She wouldn't give me any blood.
有时候有些人不愿意...
Well, sometimes people aren't willing to go through--
所以我想让你验下这个
That's why I need you to test this.
可以从这个测出来她是什么血型吧
Think you can tell me her blood type from this?
-不  不不不  -求你了
- No. Mm, no. No, no, no, no. - Please.
孩子不能没有父亲
No boy should be raised without his father.
你为什么不用检测卡碰一下这个自己去测
Well, why didn't you touch it to the card and test it yourself?
-你来了  -我来了
- Hey, you made it. - Uh, here I am.
进来吧  请随意
Oh, come on in. Get comfortable.
我帮你放起来
I'll, uh-- I'll get that for you.
我去看看饭烧糊了没有
I'll check that I didn't burn dinner.
-好的  -我帮你
- Okay. - I'll get that.
你父母在家吗
Are your parents here?
没有  他们在加里
Um, no. They live in Gary.
-这地方是你的  -没错
- This is your place? - Yeah.
二十岁
20?
-饭来了  -我才十三
- Dinner is served. - I'm only 13.
什么
What?
我才十三
I'm only 13.
你是说岁数吗
Is that, like, years old?
好吧  没事
Uh, okay. Cool.
希望你爱吃鸡肉
I hope you like chicken. -
当然  谁会不爱吃鸡肉呢
Sure. Who doesn't like chicken?
鸡肯定不爱吃鸡肉
I bet chickens don't like chicken.
想看《仓库淘宝大战》吗
Do you want to watch that Storage Wars?
-当然  看吧  -好的
- Uh, yeah, okay. - Yeah.
天啊  妈妈  三个孩子
Oh, gosh, mama. Three babies?
-我要爆炸了  -你不会有事的
- I'm gonna burst. - Oh, baby, you'll be fine.
你屁股会越长越大
Your hips gonna spread.
-给你  -谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
你得去做人流
You gonna have to have an abortion.
什么  才不要
Wh-what? Oh, hell, no.
我才不要打掉我的孩子
I'm not aborting my baby.
-我们的孩子  -我怀着的
- Our baby. - That I'm carrying.
为我俩怀的  所以
For us, so we have
我们有权决定宝宝的去留
the ultimate say in what happens to it.
这是我的身体  我才不要去做人流
Well, it's my body, and I'm not getting an abortion.
妈妈  我没办法喂饱四个小孩
Mama, I cant feed four babies.
这看起来像牛的奶子吗
Does this look like an udder?
雇个奶妈  现在酒吧归你们  该有钱了吧
Hire a wet nurse. You got money now with the bar.
更穷了
Yeah, no.
酒吧并没我们想象的那样赚钱
The bar's not making as much money as we thought.
什么
What?
凯特给我看了账目的进账项和支出项
Kate showed me the positive- negative columns in the books.
进账的基本没有几项
Positive side doesn't have much written in it.
凯文
Kevin.
我很抱歉  这不是我的错
I'm sorry. It's not my fault.
那你更是非做人流不可了  妈妈
Then you are definitely having an abortion, mother.
肯定有全天候的诊所还开着
There's got to be an all-night clinic.
等等  等等  干什么
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what?
她想要我打掉我的孩子
She wants me to abort my baby.
除非我的精子全死了
Over my dead sperm.
你刚说了  我们没钱
You just said we don't have any money.
小维  叫你妈去做人流也不问我一声
V, to ask your mom to have an abortion without consulting me,
你疯了吗  这样做是不对的
are you crazy? That's not right!
我直接朝她肚子抡一拳也行
I could punch her in the stomach.
小维
V!
凯文  我们养不起四个小孩
Kevin, we can't afford four babies!
那你在叫我跟你老公嘿咻之前
Then you should've thought about that
就该考虑到这一点的
before you made me sleep with your husband!
妈妈  我们会破产的
Mama, we'll go broke!
抱歉  但这个由上帝放进我子宫里的孩子
I'm sorry, but the good lord jesus put this baby inside my womb
代表着他赐予我的爱和光明
as a blessing to offer his love and light.
现在你要我就这么把它打掉
And now you want me to snuff it out just like that?
-绝不  -一定要
- No! - Yes!
等你清醒了再联系我  维罗妮卡
You call me when you come to your senses, Veronica.
抱歉  我很矛盾
I'm sorry. I'm conflicted.
你最好准备好滑雪面罩和逃跑座驾
You better get a ski mask and a getaway car,
因为除了抢劫  我们是绝不可能
'cause that's the only way we gonna be able
养活四个孩子的
to afford four babies.
什么事
Hey, what's up?
你刚刚下班吗
Hey, you just getting out?
是啊  漫长的一天
Yeah, man. Long day.
好的  想不想一起抽几口
Okay, yeah. You want--you want to blaze up?
不行  兄弟  我很抱歉
No, man, I'm sorry.
-得回家陪老婆  -好吧
- I got to get home to the esposa. - Okay.
如果赶不上公交车  她会杀了我的
If I miss the bus, she's gonna kill me.
-好的  兄弟  -再见  兄弟
- All right, man. - All right, see you.
再见
Yeah.
关于挡风玻璃的事
Hey, were you telling me the truth
你有没有告诉我实话
about the windshield earlier?
你不相信我吗
You don't believe me?
-我该相信你吗  -当然
- Should I? - Of course.
好吧  警察来电话了
Yeah, well, the police called,
就在你回到公司之前
like, right before you got back to the office.
是车子上公司的标志把你给卖了
It was--the logo on the car kind of totally gave you away.
你早知道
You knew?
是的  还有人用手机拍了视频
Yeah, there's even an iphone video.
会计部的泰德播给我看的
Ted in accounting showed me the YouTube.
搞什么鬼  你给我下套
What the hell? You set me up!
我...
I--
你是在因为自己对我撒谎而生气吗
You're getting angry with me because you lied?
不是  我气的是你引诱我对你撒谎
No, I'm getting angry because you tricked me into lying.
我怎么引诱你了  全是你自己说的
How did I trick you? You did it all on your own.
好  我撒谎了  行了吗
Fine, I lied! Okay?
我把那个家伙惹火了
I flipped the guy off,
他砸了我的挡风玻璃  满意了吗
and he smashed my window. Are you happy?
之前为什么不说实话
Why would you lie about that?
因为我就是这样的人  我是个加拉格
Because it's what I do. I'm a Gallagher!
省省吧  加拉格
Well, knock it off, Gallagher.
真不敢相信你会这么小题大做
I can't believe you're making such a big deal out of this.
对不起  菲奥娜
I'm sorry, Fiona.
我受不了处处是谎言的恋情
I can't be in a relationship where there's lying.
你是在给我下最后通牒吗
Are you giving me an ultimatum?
是的
Yes.
我也受不了有最后通牒的恋情
Well, I can't be in a relationship with ultimatums.
那现在怎么办
So what do we do then?
向我保证你不会再撒谎
Promise me you aren't gonna lie.
-如果我搞砸了怎么办  -承认就好
- What if I mess up? - Just admit it.
你怎么知道我的保证
How do you know I won't promise I'm not gonna lie,
不是个谎言
but that's actually a lie?
菲奥娜
Fiona,
我知道  你一定认为我反应这么大很荒唐
I know you think I'm blowing this out of proportion,
但我特别重视这个
but it's my thing.
我喜欢你
I like you.
真的很喜欢你  可如果你撒谎
I really like you, but if you lie,
我会发疯的
I'm gonna go crazy.
而且我俩都不会开心
And we'll both be unhappy,
这段恋情也会很糟
and the relationship will suck,
而我真的不想我们的恋情变质
and I really don't want this relationship to suck.
我保证  我会尽量不撒谎
I promise I'll try not to lie.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Bye.
小黛
Debs?
那人是谁
Who was that?
以免你好奇  你的血型是O型阳性
In case you're wondering, your blood type is "O" positive,
正好和弗兰克的血型一样
which happens to be the same as Frank's blood type.
你怎么知道的
How'd you find that out?
我自有办法
I've got my ways.
现在你可以捐一部分肝给他了
Now you can donate part of your liver.
你嗑药了吗
Are you high?
我磕了  他没有
I am. He's not.
退后  退后  不  老天呀
Back up, back up! No! Oh, my god!
我才不会为他挨刀子呢
There's no way I'm going under the knife for him.
他快死了
He's dying!
-跟我有什么关系  -因为他是你爸
- Why is that my problem? - Because he's your father.
他又不是天生肝有缺陷
It's not like he was dealt a bad hand, okay?
他酗酒成性  把自己的肝喝坏了
He drank through the liver that he had, and he wrecked it.
现在要来把我的也喝坏吗
And now he wants to wreck mine.
不  绝不可能
No. No way.
这回我要好好照顾自己  而不是给他擦屁股
I'm taking care of me for a change, not him.
-抱歉  卡尔  -没关系  儿子
- I'm sorry, Carl. - It's okay, son.
既然菲奥娜不肯  我只好去找另一个女儿了
If Fiona won't do it, I'll get my other daughter to.
黛比太小了
Debbie's too young.
我的大女儿  萨曼莎
My oldest daughter, Samantha.
什么
What?
三三得九
3 times 3 is 9.
四四十六
4 times 4 is 16.
五五二十五
5 times 5 is 25.
六六...
6 times 6--